<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">The 10 W&amp;H\'s</string>
    <string name="title_hint">Insert title</string>
    <string name="insert_text_hint">Insert text</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="duplicate">Duplicate</string>
    <string name="copy">Copy</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="page">Page</string>
    <string name="annuler">Cancel</string>
    <string name="all10hs">All 10 questions</string>
    <string name="onlyFilled">Only filled out questions</string>
    <string name="deleteNotice">Are you sure you want to delete this plan?</string>
    <string name="open_source_notice">The Android version of the 10 H,s app is licensed under AGPL and can be accessed here: https://github.com/overlevelsesguiden/The10H-Android</string>
    <string name="info">Children, adolescents, and adults on the autism spectrum or with ADHD and other similar disabilities often thrive on predictability and structure. Many of us experience problems with executive functions (planning, working memory, attention, problem solving etc) and therefore need to be thoroughly prepared for upcoming tasks and activities as it can quickly become confusing and overwhelming.

Getting answers to the 10 W&amp;H questions can also help to clarify expectations, add meaning, and minimize uncertainties and thereby increase motivation and reduce stress.

The 10 W&amp;H’s will also help the user to ‘see the big picture’.


The app can be used by children, adolescents and adults, both at school, at work and at home. The form can be filled in by the user or, if needed, by a parent, family member, teacher, support person etc.

The 10 W&amp;H’s include the following questions:

What to do? (Content)
Why am I doing this? (Purpose)
How do I do it? (Method)
Where do I do it? (Location)
When do I do it? (Start Time)
How long do I do it? (Time frame)
Who am I doing it with? (Person)
How much should I do? (Quantity)
Who can I get help from? (Person)
What do I do afterwards? (Content)


Using the W’s &amp; H’s is by no means a new thing. I’ve traced them all the way back to Cicero, who talked about 6 W&amp;H’s in “De Inventione”:  Who, What, Where, Why, When, and How.

Rudyard Kipling, author of The Jungle Book, wrote the following in “Just So Stories” from 1902: “I have six faithful servants. They have taught me everything I know. Their names are: What, Why, Where, How, When and Whom…”

Since then more have been added. One of the W’s I added is "Who can I get help from? I have found this to be a huge help when I get stuck and can’t move forward in an activity or task.


When you open the app, you go directly into the form with the 10 W&amp;H’s.

From there, fill in a response to each question. If you choose not to fill in all 10 W&amp;H’s, the boxes will also be blank in the completed plan.

When the form is completed, it can be printed and shared (via email or other apps). The form is converted to a PDF file, so it will not be possible for the recipient to change the text. All created forms are automatically saved in the app along with title and date.
From Android 11 onwards, you can print directly from the app via the share button. For Android 10 or earlier, a separate printer app or similar is required (eg HP, Samsung, etc.)

In the app it is possible to edit the saved forms (Press the desired form and then the Edit button. As the forms are created, they will appear on the list (which is shown when you open the app). It is of course also possible to delete forms from the list.

The app works on mobile phones with Android 8.0 or later.

I hope you will enjoy the app, and if you experience any problems, have any questions or good ideas, please send an email to: anne@overlevelsesguiden.dk</string>
    <string name="h1">What to do?</string>
    <string name="content">(content)</string>
    <string name="h2">Why am I doing this?</string>
    <string name="meaning">(purpose)</string>
    <string name="h3">How do I do it?</string>
    <string name="method">(method)</string>
    <string name="h4">Where do I do it?</string>
    <string name="place">(location)</string>
    <string name="h5">When do I do it?</string>
    <string name="time">(time)</string>
    <string name="h6">How long do I do it?</string>
    <string name="time_horizont">(time frame)</string>
    <string name="h7">Who am I doing it with?</string>
    <string name="people">(people)</string>
    <string name="h8">How much should I do?</string>
    <string name="amount">(quantity)</string>
    <string name="h9">Who can I ask for help?</string>
    <string name="person">(people)</string>
    <string name="h10">What do I do afterwards?</string>
</resources>